{"sid": "PSUJG1O80BM4_main", "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 3, "start_time": 577420, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 577421, "question": "3+97", "correct_answer": 100, "events": [["submit", 580142]], "time_left_end": "298", "answered_time": 580142, "user_answer": "100", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "298", "question_time_start": 580142, "question": "8+3+7+4", "correct_answer": 22, "events": [["submit", 583413]], "time_left_end": "295", "answered_time": 583413, "user_answer": "22", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "295", "question_time_start": 583413, "question": "7+68", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 589434]], "time_left_end": "288", "answered_time": 589434, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "288", "question_time_start": 589434, "question": "7+43", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["submit", 592846]], "time_left_end": "285", "answered_time": 592846, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "285", "question_time_start": 592846, "question": "3+6+7", "correct_answer": 16, "events": [["submit", 595495]], "time_left_end": "282", "answered_time": 595495, "user_answer": "16", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "282", "question_time_start": 595495, "question": "9+3", "correct_answer": 12, "events": [["submit", 597351]], "time_left_end": "281", "answered_time": 597351, "user_answer": "12", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "281", "question_time_start": 597351, "question": "7+3+4", "correct_answer": 14, "events": [["submit", 599604]], "time_left_end": "278", "answered_time": 599604, "user_answer": "14", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "278", "question_time_start": 599604, "question": "4+3+8+6", "correct_answer": 21, "events": [["submit", 604298]], "time_left_end": "274", "answered_time": 604298, "user_answer": "21", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "274", "question_time_start": 604298, "question": "4+4+17", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 611701]], "time_left_end": "266", "answered_time": 611701, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "266", "question_time_start": 611702, "question": "9+3", "correct_answer": 12, "events": [["submit", 613285]], "time_left_end": "265", "answered_time": 613285, "user_answer": "12", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 4, "start_time": 613285, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "265", "question_time_start": 613285, "question": "9+3+7+3", "correct_answer": 22, "events": [["submit", 616909]], "time_left_end": "261", "answered_time": 616909, "user_answer": "22", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "261", "question_time_start": 616909, "question": "8+4+6+7", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 621877]], "time_left_end": "256", "answered_time": 621877, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "256", "question_time_start": 621877, "question": "4+7+88", "correct_answer": 99, "events": [["submit", 625603]], "time_left_end": "252", "answered_time": 625603, "user_answer": "99", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "252", "question_time_start": 625603, "question": "6+4+68", "correct_answer": 78, "events": [["submit", 628659]], "time_left_end": "249", "answered_time": 628659, "user_answer": "78", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "249", "question_time_start": 628660, "question": "78+28", "correct_answer": 106, "events": [["submit", 633103]], "time_left_end": "245", "answered_time": 633103, "user_answer": "106", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "245", "question_time_start": 633103, "question": "6+9+4+8", "correct_answer": 27, "events": [["submit", 636481]], "time_left_end": "241", "answered_time": 636481, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "241", "question_time_start": 636481, "question": "7+29", "correct_answer": 36, "events": [["submit", 639111]], "time_left_end": "239", "answered_time": 639111, "user_answer": "36", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "239", "question_time_start": 639111, "question": "8+96", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 642418]], "time_left_end": "235", "answered_time": 642418, "user_answer": "104", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "235", "question_time_start": 642418, "question": "8+9+7", "correct_answer": 24, "events": [["submit", 648074]], "time_left_end": "230", "answered_time": 648074, "user_answer": "24", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "230", "question_time_start": 648075, "question": "3+8+3", "correct_answer": 14, "events": [["submit", 650754]], "time_left_end": "227", "answered_time": 650754, "user_answer": "14", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 5, "start_time": 650754, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "227", "question_time_start": 650754, "question": "7+6+3+3", "correct_answer": 19, "events": [["submit", 653767]], "time_left_end": "224", "answered_time": 653767, "user_answer": "17", "user_correct": "False", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "224", "question_time_start": 653767, "question": "3+7+69", "correct_answer": 79, "events": [["submit", 658407]], "time_left_end": "220", "answered_time": 658407, "user_answer": "79", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "220", "question_time_start": 658407, "question": "6+9+6+9", "correct_answer": 30, "events": [["submit", 663323]], "time_left_end": "215", "answered_time": 663323, "user_answer": "30", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "215", "question_time_start": 663323, "question": "6+6+17", "correct_answer": 29, "events": [["submit", 667322]], "time_left_end": "211", "answered_time": 667322, "user_answer": "29", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "211", "question_time_start": 667323, "question": "9+93", "correct_answer": 102, "events": [["submit", 671016]], "time_left_end": "207", "answered_time": 671016, "user_answer": "102", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "207", "question_time_start": 671016, "question": "23+16", "correct_answer": 39, "events": [["submit", 674874]], "time_left_end": "203", "answered_time": 674874, "user_answer": "39", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "203", "question_time_start": 674874, "question": "9+6+9+27", "correct_answer": 51, "events": [["submit", 684990]], "time_left_end": "193", "answered_time": 684990, "user_answer": "51", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "193", "question_time_start": 684990, "question": "3+7+27", "correct_answer": 37, "events": [["submit", 688009]], "time_left_end": "190", "answered_time": 688009, "user_answer": "37", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "190", "question_time_start": 688009, "question": "59+13", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["submit", 697503]], "time_left_end": "180", "answered_time": 697503, "user_answer": "62", "user_correct": "False", "score": "25"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "180", "question_time_start": 697504, "question": "9+18", "correct_answer": 27, "events": [["submit", 707005]], "time_left_end": "171", "answered_time": 707005, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 6, "start_time": 707006, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "171", "question_time_start": 707006, "question": "13+86", "correct_answer": 99, "events": [["submit", 712344]], "time_left_end": "166", "answered_time": 712344, "user_answer": "99", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "166", "question_time_start": 712344, "question": "87+26", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 717247]], "time_left_end": "161", "answered_time": 717247, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "161", "question_time_start": 717247, "question": "6+6+7+7", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 721449]], "time_left_end": "156", "answered_time": 721449, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "156", "question_time_start": 721449, "question": "4+7+6+16", "correct_answer": 33, "events": [["submit", 734108]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 734108, "user_answer": "33", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 734109, "question": "9+8+16", "correct_answer": 33, "events": [["submit", 741082]], "time_left_end": "137", "answered_time": 741082, "user_answer": "33", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "137", "question_time_start": 741082, "question": "27+84", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 745639]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 745639, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 745639, "question": "8+88+53", "correct_answer": 149, "events": [["submit", 756773]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 756773, "user_answer": "149", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 756773, "question": "7+7+97", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 775281]], "time_left_end": "103", "answered_time": 775281, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "103", "question_time_start": 775281, "question": "7+9+4+17", "correct_answer": 37, "events": [["submit", 786071]], "time_left_end": "92", "answered_time": 786071, "user_answer": "37", "user_correct": "True", "score": "35"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "92", "question_time_start": 786071, "question": "3+7+8+9", "correct_answer": 27, "events": [["submit", 791048]], "time_left_end": "87", "answered_time": 791048, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "True", "score": "36"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 791048, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "87", "question_time_start": 791048, "question": "3+66+37", "correct_answer": 106, "events": [["submit", 794467]], "time_left_end": "83", "answered_time": 794467, "user_answer": "106", "user_correct": "True", "score": "37"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "83", "question_time_start": 794468, "question": "97+79", "correct_answer": 176, "events": [["submit", 802173]], "time_left_end": "76", "answered_time": 802173, "user_answer": "176", "user_correct": "True", "score": "38"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "76", "question_time_start": 802173, "question": "4+8+4+27", "correct_answer": 43, "events": [["submit", 812735]], "time_left_end": "65", "answered_time": 812735, "user_answer": "43", "user_correct": "True", "score": "39"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "65", "question_time_start": 812735, "question": "9+4+3+46", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 818475]], "time_left_end": "59", "answered_time": 818475, "user_answer": "62", "user_correct": "True", "score": "40"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "59", "question_time_start": 818475, "question": "24+588", "correct_answer": 612, "events": [["submit", 832382]], "time_left_end": "46", "answered_time": 832382, "user_answer": "612", "user_correct": "True", "score": "41"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "46", "question_time_start": 832382, "question": "3+9+28", "correct_answer": 40, "events": [["submit", 837401]], "time_left_end": "41", "answered_time": 837401, "user_answer": "40", "user_correct": "True", "score": "42"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "41", "question_time_start": 837401, "question": "7+6+8+23", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 843900]], "time_left_end": "34", "answered_time": 843900, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "43"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "34", "question_time_start": 843900, "question": "9+99+73", "correct_answer": 181, "events": [["submit", 857359]], "time_left_end": "21", "answered_time": 857359, "user_answer": "181", "user_correct": "True", "score": "44"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "21", "question_time_start": 857359, "question": "43+33", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 861294]], "time_left_end": "17", "answered_time": 861294, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "45"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "17", "question_time_start": 861295, "question": "3+7+17", "correct_answer": 27, "events": [["submit", 865906]], "time_left_end": "12", "answered_time": 865906, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "True", "score": "46"}}}, "block_5": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 865906, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "12", "question_time_start": 865906, "question": "3+39+49", "correct_answer": 91, "events": [["submit", 876274]], "time_left_end": "2", "answered_time": 876274, "user_answer": "92", "user_correct": "False", "score": "45"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "2", "question_time_start": 876275, "question": "7+28+13", "correct_answer": 48, "events": []}}}}}